What the hell is that?!
誰在鬼叫？
What the hell is that? Is that you?
誰在鬼叫？是你嗎？
-You're really not a morning person. -Just back off!
你清晨的火氣還真大 滾遠一點
Get up! Get up! Get up!
起來！…
What is that noise?
那是什麼聲音？
You!
是你的敲門聲！
It's the chick.
是小雞啦
She's going through some changes.
它正歷經過度時期
What kind of changes?
什麼過度時期？
The vet seems to think...
獸醫認為…
...she's becoming a rooster.
咱們的小母雞要長大成公雞了
We're getting a second opinion.
我們打算再問問別的獸醫
The One With the Embryos
本集播出：公寓大搬風
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Why are you shopping at 8 in the morning?
你幹嘛清晨八點去血拼？
I've been up since 6...
我六點鐘就起床了
...thanks to somebody's dumb-ass rooster.
都是被某人的笨公雞害的
You should get rid of those animals. They shouldn't be in an apartment.
你們應該把它們處理掉 它們不應該窩在公寓裡
Especially not with these knives and cookbooks around.
是啊，特別是這裡 又有那麼多刀和食譜
I'm going to the doctor and see if I'm ready...
我要去看婦產科醫生
...to have Frank and Alice's embryo transferred into my uterus.
看看能不能把法蘭克和艾莉絲的胚胎 移植到我的子宮裡去
How will they know?
他們怎麼知道你準備好了沒？
They'll just see if my endometrial layer is thick.
他們要看看我的子宮內膜 是不是已經增厚了
I can check that for you.
我幫你看就好了
Okay,think "thick."
各位，幫我的子宮內膜加油吧
Good luck!
祝你好運
Wish me luck.
快祝我幸運
Good luck.
祝你好運
-I'm still right. -That is so not true.
我說得沒錯啦 鬼扯
What?
I know it's her laundry day...
她不爽是因為我知道 她今天要洗衣服
...and that means she's wearing her old-lady underpants.
所以現在穿的是老奶奶大內褲
I can check that for you.
要不要我檢查一下？
You two think you know me and Rachel...
你們憑什麼認為 比瑞秋和我...
...better than we know you.
...更瞭解我們？
Well,we do.
本來就是
You can only eat Tic Tacs in even numbers.
你吃薄荷糖時一定要吃偶數
What's that about?
你有什麼毛病啊？
And you! Ross,if you check Rachel's bag...
而你嘛… 羅斯，你去搜搜瑞秋的購物袋
...you'll find a half-eaten box of cookies in there.
裡面一定有一盒 吃了一半的餅乾
You're good.
高明
These are not.
這包餅乾就不怎麼高明了
I'm so not impressed. Everybody snacks when they shop.
有什麼了不起 哪有人買東西時不吃零嘴？
Ross,how many items left in that bag?
是嗎？羅斯，購物袋裡 還有幾樣東西？
Five.
五樣
Okay,10 bucks says we can name every item in that bag.
賭十塊，我們能說出 那五樣東西是什麼
-How many guesses? -Six.
你們能猜幾次？ 六次
Challenge extended.
男生隊下戰書
-Deal! -Challenge accepted.
賭就賭 女生隊接受挑戰
All right,we'll start with...
第一樣是…
...apples.
...蘋果
We'll be starting with apples.
我們就從蘋果開始
Stop that now.
拜託你住嘴
Yes.
有蘋果
Okay. Tortilla chips.
玉米片
-Yogurt. -Diet soda.
優格 健怡汽水
對…
-Orange juice. -There's no orange juice! We win!
柳橙汁 我沒買柳橙汁，我們贏了！
They have another guess.
等等，他們還能再猜一次
Well,we won that one.
但是那題我們贏了
Okay. The last thing is
最後一樣東西是…
Not for another two weeks.
不是…還要等兩周
I got it.
我知道了
Scotch...
膠…
...tape.
帶
How did you know she would buy Scotch tape?
你怎麼知道她會買膠帶？
We used up theirs last night making scary faces.
我們昨晚玩扮鬼臉時 把她們的膠帶用光了
Oh,man!
討厭
All right! Ten bucks. Fork it over.
十塊錢，願賭服輸
Cough it up. Pay the piper.
甘願點
Give me it!
拿錢來
You don't know us better. I want a rematch.
這沒什麼了不起 我要再比一次
And no stupid grocery questions. Real,personal questions.
猜雜貨沒挑戰性 這次要問切身問題
And the winner gets $100.
賭一百塊
-Serious? -Are you scared?
你當真？ 怕了？
No.
才怪
Who makes up the questions?
誰出考題？
Ross will do it.
羅斯
Sure,Ross will do it.
是啊，找羅斯
It's not like he has a job or a child or a life of his own.
反正他沒工作，沒兒子 生活又無聊
-Fine. We'll ask Phoebe. -No,I want to play.
好嘛，那找菲比好了 不要，人家想玩嘛
Looks like your uterus is ready for implantation.
你的子宮可以做胚胎移植了
I knew it! I felt really thick this morning.
我就知道 我今天早上就覺得厚厚的
Okay,so what's now? Go get the eggs. Put them in there.
現在怎麼辦？ 快去把卵子放進去
It'll take a little while to prepare the embryos.
我要花點時間準備那些胚胎
-Embryos? As in more than one? -Five,actually.
那些胚胎？不只一個？ 事實上，一共有五個
Where am I giving birth...
五個？
...in a hospital or a big box under the stairs?
你把我當母豬啊？
Doing five gives you a 25% chance that at least one will attach.
植入五個胚胎 表示著床機率大概是25%
That's it? 25%?
25%？這麼少？
That means that it's,like, 75% chance of no baby at all?
這表示我生不出小孩的機率 是75%？
I was thinking, what are the odds...
那如果兩百個胚胎進去
...if you stuff 200 of them in there?
機率會不會高一點？
Sweetie,now...
親愛的，
...she's a woman, not a gumball machine.
她是個女人 不是賣泡泡糖的機器
Don't worry. I'll do this as many times as it takes to get it right.
別擔心 我會一直做到成功為止
The thing is,we kind of only have one shot.
但是我們只有一次機會
It costs $16,000 each time you do this.
做一次移植要花一萬六千塊
Sixteen thousand dollars?!
一萬六千塊？
Well,it's 20 in California.
我們已經比加州便宜了
We're kind of using all the money we have to do it this one time.
我們為了這一次 已經花光所有的積蓄
Okay,that's a lot of pressure on me and my uterus.
天啊，這讓我和我的子宮 壓力超大
Maybe there's something I can do to make sure I get pregnant.
也許我能做些什麼事 來提高懷孕的機率
No,I'm sorry.
沒有
Wow,you guys really don't know anything.
你們真是啥都不懂
Why don't you get drunk? It worked for a bunch of girls in my high school.
那她喝個爛醉如何？ 我很多高中同學 都是這樣搞大肚子的
-So how's the test coming? -Hey,you're touching the game board.
問題準備得如何？ 別亂動
Sorry.
抱歉啦
You freak.
怪胎
Do you realize that any minute now...
你們知道菲比現在
...Phoebe could be pregnant?
隨時可能會懷孕嗎？
I know,I know.
我知道…
It's such a huge, life-altering thing.
這件事真是非同小可 是啊
The test is ready.
考題準備好了
Okay. Each team will answer 10 questions.
每一隊都要回答十個問題
The first team to answer the most questions wins.
答對最多的那一隊就贏
The categories are "Fears and Pet Peeves"...
考題項目如下… 「恐懼和怪癖」
..."Ancient History"...
「陳年往事」
..."Literature"...
「文學」
...and "It's all Relative."
和「日常瑣事」
Now...
...the coin toss, to see who goes first.
我們丟硬幣來決定哪一隊先攻
Okay.
Somebody call it this time.
拜託你們先猜哪一面
Tails!
字
It's heads.
是人頭
Gentlemen,pick your category.
男生隊，請挑項目
"Fears and Pet Peeves."
「恐懼和怪癖」
"What is Monica's biggest pet peeve?"
摩妮卡最受不了什麼？
-Animals dressed as humans. -Correct.
動物穿衣服 答對了
-Ladies? -Same category.
女生隊？ 同一個項目
"According to Chandler,what phenomenon scares the bejesus out of him?"
錢德最怕什麼東西？
Michael Flatley,Lord of the Dance!
踢踏舞之王麥克費特利
That is correct.
答對了
The lrish jig guy?
那個跳舞的愛爾蘭人？
His legs flail about as if independent from his body!
他那雙腳跳舞時 好像跟身體分離了一樣
Gentlemen,your pick.
男生隊，輪到你們了
"It's all Relative."
「日常瑣事」
"Monica and I had a grandmother who died.
摩妮卡和我的祖母過世時
You both went to her funeral.
兩位都參加了她的葬禮
Name that grandmother."
我們祖母叫什麼名字？
-Nana? -She has a real name.
姥姥？ 她有個真正的名字吧
Althea!
艾席雅
-What? -I took a shot!
什麼？ 試試看嘛
With Althea?
那幹嘛猜艾席雅？
-Althea is correct. -Nice shooting!
答對了 猜得好
"Literature."
「文學」
"Every week the TV Guide comes to Chandler and Joey's apartment.
喬伊和錢德 每週都會收到「電視週刊」
What name appears on the address label?"
請問收件人的姓名為何？
Chandler gets it! It's Chandler Bing!
錢德訂的，當然是錢德賓羅
I'm afraid the TV Guide comes to "Chanandler Bong."
不是啦 「電視週刊」收件人的姓名 是「錢尼德勒邦」
I knew that!
我知道正確答案
Rachel,use your head!
瑞秋，用用腦子行不行？
Actually,it's Ms. Chanandler Bong.
事實上 應該是「錢尼德勒邦小姐」
Hello,teeny embryos.
嗨，各位小胚胎
I'm Phoebe Buffay. Hi!
我是菲比
I'm hoping to be your uterus for the next nine months.
我的子宮 就是各位未來九個月的家
We're doing this for Frank and Alice...
我們這麼做 都是為了法蘭克和艾莉絲
...who you know. You've been there.
你們跟他們應該很熟
They want you so much.
他們真的很希望能有個小寶寶
So when you guys get in there, really grab on.
你們進去之後好好抓緊
And I promise that I'll keep you safe and warm...
我保證會讓你們 住得又舒服又安全
...until you're ready to have them take you home.
直到你們準備好 讓他們帶你們回家為止
Next time you see me, if I'm screaming,don't worry.
咱們下次見面時 我應該會雞貓子喊叫
That's what's supposed to happen.
請別擔心，這是很正常的
Ready?
準備好了嗎？
Good luck!
祝好運
The score is nine to eight in favor of the guys.
目前比數是九比八 男生隊領先
Ladies,if you miss this, the game is theirs. Pick a category.
女生隊若答錯這題 男生隊就贏了 選一個項目吧
"It's all Relative"!
「日常瑣事」
-You don't have to shout everything. -I'm sorry!
犯不著拉直嗓子吼 對不起！
"What is the name of Chandler's father's...
錢德父親在賭城的男子歌舞秀
...Las Vegas all-male burlesque?"
叫做什麼名字？
Viva Las Gaygas!
「同志萬歲」
Unfortunately,that is correct.
很不幸的…你答對了
All right. We have a tie.
目前雙方平手
Luckily,I've prepared for such an event.
不過我早有準備了
The lightning round!
搶答
Thirty seconds. All the questions you can answer.
雙方各有30秒搶答
You guys are dead!
你們輸定了
I am so good at lightning rounds!
我超會搶答
I majored in lightning rounds, all right?
我大學是主修搶答的
We'll destroy you.
你們才輸定了
Want to bet?
敢不敢賭？
I'm so confused as to what we've been doing so far.
怪了，我們這不正是在賭嗎？
How about we play for more money? Say 150?
把賭注提高到… 150塊如何？
One hundred and fifty dollars.
150塊
Say 200?
200塊如何？
Two hundred dollars!
200塊
You're doing it again.
你又來了
Excuse me.
不好意思
-I don't want to lose $200. -We won't.
我不想輸200塊 我們不會輸的
Three hundred?
300塊如何？ 摩妮卡
I'm spicing it up!
我只是想讓比賽更香辣有勁
So play for some pepper! Stop spending my money.
賭辣椒行不行？ 別再亂花我的錢了
I got it!
我有了
If we win,they have to get rid of the rooster.
我們贏的話 他們就得處理掉那只公雞
That's interesting!
有意思
-No way! That rooster's family. -The duck too!
不行，公雞和我們是一家人 還有那只鴨
The duck doesn't make noise!
幹嘛扯上那只鴨？它又不亂叫
He gets the other one all riled up!
那隻雞被它搞得心浮氣躁
-We are not -All right,hold on!
聽著，我們絕不… 等等
If you win...
你們贏的話
...we give up the bird.
我們就處理掉那只公雞
But if we win...
我們贏的話…
...we get your apartment.
就把你們的公寓讓給我們
-Deal! -What?
成交 什麼？
That's crazy. There's no way we are betting the apartment.
這太扯了，我絕不拿公寓來賭
All right,I'm in. Because either he goes,or I'm buying a coyote.
好，我賭了！ 那隻雞不走我就要買隻狼
Betting the apartment? I don't know about this.
拿公寓來賭好像不太穩當
I have not missed one question the whole game. I own this game!
瑞秋，我從頭到尾 一題都沒答錯 我會贏的！
-Look at my hand. -You have the answers written there?
看我的手 你手上有寫小抄嗎？
No. Steady as a rock. Now,are you with me?
不是啦，我的手穩得很 你還不放心嗎？
All right,let's do it!
咱們上陣吧 這樣才對
All right. Gentlemen,you're up first.
男生隊先攻
You have 30 seconds.
限時搶答30秒
The lightning round begins
搶答階段要開始了…
Stop it!
不准跳
"Monica's nickname when she was a hockey goalie?"
摩妮卡當曲棍球隊 守門員的外號為何？
-Big Fat Goalie. -Correct!
胖球門 正確
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
瑞秋宣稱 她最喜歡的電影為何？
Dangerous Liaisons.
「危險關係」
-"Her actual favorite is...?" -Weekend at Bernie's.
她真正喜歡的電影是哪一部？ 「玩死老弟」
"In what part of her body did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?"
摩妮卡14歲時 身上哪個部位卡了一枝鉛筆？
No!
惡…
Her ear!
是她的耳朵
"Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?"
摩妮卡的毛巾都分門別類 一共分為幾類？
-Everyday use. -Fancy.
日常用毛巾 高級毛巾
-Guest. -Fancy guest.
客用毛巾 高級客用毛巾
-Two seconds. -Eleven?
還剩兩秒鐘 11類？
Unbelievable! Eleven is correct!
不可思議，答對了
All right.
太好了…
That's four for the guys. Ladies,you're up!
男生隊答對四題 現在輪女生隊搶答
Thirty seconds on the clock.
限時搶答30秒
Five correct questions wins the game.
答對五題你們就贏了
The lightning round begins now. "Joey's favorite food?"
搶答開始 喬伊最喜歡的食物為何？
-Sandwiches! -Correct.
三明治 正確
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
錢德第一次 摸女生胸部是幾歲？
-14? -No,19.
14歲？ 不，19
Thanks,man.
謝了，老哥
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
喬伊小時有個幻想中的朋友
-His name was...?" -Maurice!
他的名字叫… 莫瑞斯
-"His profession was...?" -Space cowboy!
正確，他的職業是… 太空牛仔
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
錢德賓的工作為何？
It has something to do with numbers!
跟數字有關
-And processing! -He carries a briefcase.
還有處理 他上班帶公事包
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose.
剩10秒鐘，答錯就輸了
Something to do with transponding.
跟答詢有關
He's a transponster!
他是答詢員
That's not even a word!
哪有這種字？
I can get this! I can get this!
我知道…
不… 爽…
-I call Monica's room. -You can't just call Monica's room.
我要摩妮卡的房間 這哪是你說要就要的
Sure I can. Standard shotgun rules.
哪不是，先下手為強
I'm in sight of the room and I called it.
誰叫你不先要
Damn!
（可惡）
I feel like I'm coming down with something.
我好像要生病了
Guess the color of my tonsils. I bet the apartment!
要不要猜猜我的扁桃腺 是什麼顏色？ 用公寓來賭
I would never bet this place. It's too nice.
我才不會拿 這麼棒的公寓來賭呢
Are they in there?
菲比，你肚子裡有東西了嗎？
Yeah,I'm implanted.
對，胚胎放進去了
-How do you feel? -Well,freaked.
你覺得怎麼樣？ 擔心死了
It turns out the odds are really sucky.
成功的機率不高
And this is Frank and Alice's only shot.
但法蘭克和艾莉絲 只有這次機會
They are literally putting all their eggs in my basket.
他們把所有的蛋 都放在我的籃子裡
But I bet it works.
我相信你一定會成功
Really? How much?
是嗎？你要賭多少？
I'm going to take a pregnancy test now.
我現在就去驗孕
Wow! You can tell this soon?
這麼快？
The doctor says it takes a few days.
醫生說要等兩天
But my body's always been a little faster than Western medicine.
但是我的身體 一向比西方醫學快一點
I can't believe you guys think you're moving in here.
天啊 你們真以為能搬進來？
Well,believe it,baby!
面對現實吧，寶貝
-Well,I'm not moving. -What?
我不走 什麼？
No. It was a stupid bet. We were just playing a game.
那不過是場愚蠢的賭局 玩玩罷了
You can't ignore the bet. It's a bet!
賭就賭了，哪能不算
Bet on a bet and if you lose,you lose the bet.
賭輸就是輸了
We have to move.
我們非搬不可
We would have made them get rid of the birds.
若我們贏了 也會逼他們把雞鴨處理掉
才怪
I hate this as much as you, but if it makes you feel better...
我也不想這樣 但說句安慰你的話…
...this is all your fault.
這全都是你的錯
What?
什麼？
Chanandler Bong! We steal that TV Guide every week!
我們每週都偷他們的電視週刊 你怎麼會不知道收件人是誰？
I knew it!
我就知道
I don't care. I'm not going anywhere.
我不管，我不走
Cool! Girl roommate.
酷啊，跟女生做室友
Well?
怎麼樣？
Nope,not knocked up yet.
我的肚子還沒被搞大
It's only been a couple hours.
才過兩個小時耶，耐心點
Meanwhile,I'll do whatever I can to help this.
我也要為這件事盡一份力
I'm just going to,you know, lie in your chair,okay?
讓我躺在你們的椅子上
Good. I'm going to let gravity do its job.
讓地心引力發揮作用
I won't get in the way.
我不會礙事的
It'll be just like that time I tried to count all the bumps on your ceiling.
就像我那次躺在這裡 數天花板上的蟲子一樣
You know,Pheebs,if you sit there long enough,you'll be sitting in our apartment.
菲比，你若坐得夠久 這裡就會變成我們的公寓
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
Oh,Rach,FYl: Your new apartment hasn't had hot water since Christmas.
瑞秋，有件事忘了告訴你 你那間新公寓 自聖誕節後就沒熱水了
Can you give me a hand?
瑞秋，過來幫我搬這個箱子
Put that box down! We are not going anywhere!
不，把箱子放下來 我們哪兒都不去
This is my apartment and I like it!
這是我的公寓，我喜歡它
This is a girl's apartment!
這是女生的公寓
That is a boy's apartment! It's dirty and it smells!
那裡才是又髒又臭的男生公寓
This is pretty! It's so pretty!
這裡漂亮死了…
And look,it's purple!
看，牆壁是紫的
I tell you,you with your steady hand,I am not moving.
穩若磐石小姐，我不搬
And now I have got the steady hand.
看，我的手也穩若磐石
Okay,okay.
好…
-I'll take care of it. -That's right.
我去搞定 這才乖
You do what the hand says!
照我手的話去做
-How'd it go? -I lost our mattresses.
情況如何？ 我把床墊輸掉了
Are you in there,little fetus? In nine months will you come greet us?
小胎兒，你在裡面嗎？ 九個月後是否就能夠相見？
I will buy you some Adidas
我會幫你買阿迪達斯
We were just at the drugstore so we got you a little present.
我們剛剛去過藥妝店 幫你買了個小禮物
That's where all my blood was.
天啊，腦充血
It's a lollipop and a home pregnancy test.
棒棒糖和驗孕棒
Don't mix those up. You could really ruin that lollipop.
別搞混了，棒棒糖沾尿很噁心
You feel like taking a test? There's only one question.
想不想驗一下？一次定生死
All right. I will.
我驗就是了
Remember that it's still really early.
別忘了，現在還早
If it says I'm not pregnant,that doesn't mean I won't get pregnant.
若結果是陰性 不表示我不會懷孕
Just so I don't go completely nuts...
拜託你們別寄望太高
...try not to put all your hopes on this.
否則會把我逼瘋的
好
Great.
好極了
You are mean boys who are just being mean!
你們真是壞到骨子裡去了
Don't get mad! No one forced you to raise the stakes.
別把氣出在我們身上 沒人逼你們把公寓拿來賭
That is not true! She forced me!
亂講，她有逼我
You got the question wrong.
答錯的人是你啊
It was a stupid,unfair question!
那個問題太不公平了
Don't blame the questions!
別怪我出的問題
Stop yelling in our apartment! You are ruining moving day for us.
別在我們家大吵大鬧 掃了我們的搬家興
-Stop calling it your apartment! -lt is!
別說這裡是你們家 本來就是
You're going to have a baby. They're going to have a baby!
你們要有寶寶了 他們要有寶寶了
My sister's going to have my baby!
我姐姐要幫我生小孩了
Okay,but this can't be good for the baby.
別抱了，這對寶寶不好
I can't find garbage bags.
我找不到垃圾袋
I think I saw some in here.
這裡面好像有
What is it?
什麼東西？
I don't know. But maybe if we keep that drawer shut,it'll die.
不知道，要是把抽屜關上 它也許會死
I can't believe we're living here!
真不敢相信我們得住在這裡
What is it?
什麼事？
Did you see the size of the closets?
你知道衣櫥有多大嗎？
I can't believe we live here!
不敢相信咱們可以住在這裡